<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ujian Praktek UTS Semester 1 Kelas 11</string>
    <string name="adidas1">Pharrell and adidas Originals have presented a veritable cornucopia of co-created silhouettes since they officially became partners in 2014, and now the dynamic duo have yet another chapter in their storied NMD Hu Trail saga set to begin: the rugged lifestyle sneaker has appeared in a new “Sun/Calm” colorway. Using a soft and mellow powder pink upper, Skateboard P’s newest shoes continue his ethos of boundless positivity and neverending love by featuring “Calm” and “Sun” motifs presented via tonal embroidery on the left and right feet, respectively. The midfoot cage and midsole blocks offer more of the pink hue, while flecked pink/silver laces present just enough reflective detailing. The thick white Boost midsole offers comfort and style in equal measures, while a classic gum outsole finalizes the look.</string>
    <string name="adidas2">The new adidas Originals EQT Support 93/17 silhouette returns in a new color configuration, continuing the bold evolution of the 3-stripes’ iconic Equipment series. Returning to the shoe’s original material makeup, this release sees the EQT Support 93/17’s signature woven upper rendered in a white pixelated noise motif, countered with premium leather panels and the EQT series’ signature webbed 3-stripes lacing system. Finishing touches include essential TPU ankle supports, an external heel cage, OrthoLite sockliner and the shoe’s iconic extended 3-stripes along the midsole. Contrasting black and white colors on the lateral and medial sides create an edition that looks truly distinct from every angle, united through a striking hit of EQT Turbo Red around the ankle support.</string>
    <string name="adidas3">The adidas Originals Yung 1, a current favorite amongst sneaker lovers is part of the super anticipated Dragon Ball Z x adidas collaboration. The chunky trainer comes dressed in the colors or Freiza, the emperor of Universe 7, a descendant of Chilled – and the bad guy – iconic antagonist who fought with Goku on Namek and invaded earth not just once. The recurring villain serves as the blueprint for the adidas Originals Yung 1, dressing the shoe in a white, purple and pink mesh and nubuck upper to pay homage to the Vicious God.</string>
    <string name="adidas4">Inspired by the pioneering spirit of running designs from the mid-\'80s, the NMD series celebrates a time when wearable technology was exciting and new. These shoes translate the retro-tech style for today\'s streets with a modern knit upper.and a Boost midsole.</string>
    <string name="adidas5">new of the four Ultra Boosts that dropped in the October 2016 \'reflective pack,\' this variant is a mix of core black and white on the gradient Primeknit upper with 3M reflective accents, a white Boost midsole, and a white Continental Rubber outsole.</string>
    <string name="nike1">The ACRONYM x Nike Air Presto Mid was first introduced in 2016, and for this year, the silhouette is coming back in three brand new iterations. Textile/mesh construction with synthetics and leather accents, zippering system on the extended collar area for easy accessibility and additional support, graphic print pattern on the lacing cage apparatus and toe cap, heel pull tabs.</string>
    <string name="nike2">The Sacai x LDV Waffle fuses the Japanese label\'s experimentalism with Nike\'s heritage ingenuity. Unveiled in September 2019, this \'Pine Green\' edition updates the hybrid model in a vibrant color story. Its mesh upper sees layered suede eyestays, double reinforcements and dual, two-tone Swooshes. The aesthetic is furthered by twin tongues, optional double laces and stacked heel logos. Its double stacked, sculpted midsole follows the same formula atop a rubber waffle tread.</string>
    <string name="nike3">This kick has been considered one of the highly coveted Yeezy pairs in the market. ... The Nike Air Yeezy 2 Red October comes with stylish and exclusive drawstring bag. The unique details of this model are praiseworthy according to a few reviewers. The glow in the dark sole has been lauded by some fans.</string>
    <string name="nike4">Air Max 1 Have a Nike Day. Your day will instantly become better after grabbing the Air Max 1 Have a Nike Day. This AM 1 comes with a multi-color upper, black Nike “Swoosh”, white midsole, and a multi-color sole. These sneakers released in March 2019.</string>
    <string name="nike5">This Kyrie 5 features a bright pink upper with a green and purple sole. The upper has detailing of speckles and texture to represent the surface of a starfish. Nickelodeon logos on the straps, title-font inspired Nike branding on the heel, and Patrick graphics on the insoles completes the design.</string>
    <string name="nb1"><![CDATA[The Kith x New Balance 997 &quot;United Arrows & Sons&quot; is a premium collaboration from Ronnie Fieg and New Balance. The color palette is a modified representation of a classic New Balance 997 by Japan’s United Arrows & Sons from 2009. The impressive construction features a light grey pigskin suede base with purple and bright pink accents and a black tongue. A cream-colored midsole creates a vintage effect, while special details like an added “997” tab and alternating colors for the lettering of the New Balance logo on each heel tab complete the design. The Kith x New Balance 997 “United Arrows & Sons” released in limited quantities in November 2018, and instantly became another highly sought-after collaboration from Fieg and New Balance.]]></string>
    <string name="nb2">The Kith x United Arrows and Sons x New Balance 997S is a collaboration that originally released in November 2018. It is inspired by one of Ronnie Fieg\'s favorite New Balance collabs, the United Arrows\' 997.5 from 2009, that was notably worn by Kanye West. The remixed 997, the 997S, features updates like a neoprene sock collar and a lighter build. A grey pigskin suede and mesh upper features details like pebbled leather overlays on the midfoot and heel tab. Pink and purple accents are also used across the upper. A triple-stacked \"N\" logo on each side panel and an ENCAP Reveal-cushioned midsole complete the design.</string>
    <string name="nb3">New York-based Engineered Garments and New England reppin’ New Balance come together to give the latest update of the 990V5 a new theme. The three colorways available take their idea from the originally available 990s, and this grey iteration might be the most famous one. The contrasting shades of grey with tonal alligator-like leather give the Engineered Garments x New Balance 900 a fresh look, classic, but with a twist, that makes it even more desirable.</string>
    <string name="nb4">&quot;K&quot; branding on the 997S’ tongue matches the logo on the tall OMN1s sneaker, also bolstered by hits of gold across the upper. The shiny lace loops sit atop a cool-hued knit, complete with a stretchy strap that keeps the wearer’s foot in place. Black leather and mesh near the ankle aid the white midsole in grounding the hefty shoe, which is completed with black “NB” branding set into its translucent outsole.</string>
    <string name="nb5">A fan-favourite silhouette in best-in-the-business grey, this American-made 997 from New Balance is a reimagining of the classic. With an upper exactly as expected – from the luxe pigskin suede to the reflective 3M ‘N’ sidewall logo – the underfoot has been altered to match modern demands. Maintaining the all-important ENCAP® technology, the sole has been taken from the brand’s ‘sport’ models, altering the sneaker’s lines while maintaining the overall aesthetic sneakerheads all know and love.</string>

    <string-array name="metodePengiriman">
        <item>Instant</item>
        <item>Same Day</item>
        <item>Regular</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="metodePembayaran">
        <item>Cash On Delivery</item>
        <item>Debit</item>
        <item>Credit</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
